L. C. Dunn Papers ca.1920-1974 Mss.B.D917
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1920-1974 (Box 1)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1924-1974; 1,080 items (Box 16)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 June 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Sept. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Sept. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Oct. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Oct. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Dec. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Dec. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Dec. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Jan. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Jan. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Jan. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Feb. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Feb. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 March 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 March 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 April 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 April 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 May 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 July 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Aug. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Sept. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Sept. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1937 Dec. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Jan. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Feb. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Aug. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Sept. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Oct. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1938 Nov. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Nov. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Nov. 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Dec. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1938 Dec. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Jan. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Feb. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 April 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 May 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1939] June 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Sept. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Sept. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Oct. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1939 Nov. 11] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1939 Dec. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 March 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 April 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 April 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 May 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 June 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 June 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 July 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1940] July 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 July 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 August 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 August 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 August 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 Sept. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - Louise Dunn to Walter Landauer, 1940 October 30 (Box 17-19)
    - Walter Landauer to Louise Dunn, 1940 ca. Oct. 30 (Box 17-19)
    - Louise Dunn to Walter Landauer, 1940 November 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1940 November 24 (Box 17-19)
    - Walter Landauer to Louise Dunn, 1940 November 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Feb. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 March 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 March 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1941 March 11] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 April 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 June 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 June 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 June 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Aug. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Oct. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Nov. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Nov. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1941 Dec. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1942 Jan. 27] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 June 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 July 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1942 Aug. 18] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Sept. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Sept. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Sept. 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Oct. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Nov. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Dec. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1942 Dec. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1943 Feb. 11] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Feb. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 April 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 April 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 May 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 June 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Aug. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Sept. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Oct. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Oct. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1943 Nov. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Jan. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Jan. 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Feb. 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 March 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 April 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 May 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 July 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Aug. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Aug. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Sept. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Sept. 23 (Box 17-19)
      (Contains letter of Olaf Neilsen to Dunn, July 14 [1940])
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Oct. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Oct. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1944 Nov. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 Jan. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 Feb. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 Feb. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 July 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 July (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 Sept. 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1945 Sept. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1945 Sept.] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Jan. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 April 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 May 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1946 May 6] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Aug. 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Aug. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1946 Sept. 16] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Oct. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Oct. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1946 Dec. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn (Includes A. Roettcher-Mertine to Landauer, 17 Nov. 1946), 1947 Jan. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Feb. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Feb. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 March 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 April 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 June 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 July 22-24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Aug. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 August 25-29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Oct. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Oct. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Oct. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 Nov. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 December 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1947 December 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1947] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Jan. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 January (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1948 March 14] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 May 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1948] July 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 July 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1948] Aug. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Aug. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1948] Aug. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Sept. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Oct. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Nov. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1948 Nov. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1948 Dec. 24] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1949 Feb. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1949 May 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1949 May 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1949 Aug. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1949 Sept. 29] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1950 Jan. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1950 Feb. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1950 June 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1950 Sept. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1951 Jan. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1951 Feb. 23] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1951 March 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1951 Sept. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1951 Oct. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1951 Nov. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1951 Dec. 12] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 Jan 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 March 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 March 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 July 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 July 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1952 July 30] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 Aug. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 Oct. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1952 Nov. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1953 Jan. 19] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1953 Feb. 25] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 March 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 March 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 April 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 May 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 July 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 Oct. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 Nov. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1953 Dec. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 Jan. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 April 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 May 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 June 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 Aug. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 Oct. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 Oct. 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1954 Nov. 17] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1954 Nov. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1955 Jan. 12] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Jan. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Jan. 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Feb. 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 April 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1955 April 19] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 May 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 June 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 June 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Sept. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Oct. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Oct. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Oct. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1955 Nov. 17] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1955 Nov. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Jan. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Feb. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Feb. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 April 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 April 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 May 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 July 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Aug. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Sept. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Sept. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Sept. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Dec. 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1956 Dec. 23] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1956 Dec. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1957 May 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1957 Dec. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Jan. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Jan. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Jan. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Jan. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Feb. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 March 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 April 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 April 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 May 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 June 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 July 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Oct. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Nov. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Nov. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Nov. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Dec. 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1958 Dec. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1959 Jan. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1959 Jan. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1959 Jan. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1961 July 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1961 July 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1961 Oct. 24] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1961 Oct. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 March 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 April 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 April 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 July 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1962 Aug. 14] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 Sept. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 Oct. 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1962 Dec. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 Jan. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 Feb. 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 Feb. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 March 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 May 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 July 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 July 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1963] Oct. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1963 Nov. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Jan. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Jan. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Jan. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Feb. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Feb. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 April 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 April 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 June 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 July 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Aug. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Sept. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Nov. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1964 Dec. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 Feb. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 Feb. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 March 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 March 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 April 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 April 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 April 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 May 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 May 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 June 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 July 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 Aug. 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1965 Sept. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1965 Dec.] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 Jan. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 Feb. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 April 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 April 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 May 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 May 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 July 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 July 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 Aug. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1966 Sept. 6] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1966 Nov. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1966] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Jan. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Jan. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Feb. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 March 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 May 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 July 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Nov. 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Dec. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Dec. 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1967 Dec. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 Jan. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 Jan. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 Feb. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 June 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 July 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 Aug. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1968 Aug. 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 April 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 May 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1969 June 30] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 Aug. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 Sept. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 Dec. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1969 Dec. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 Feb. 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 March 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 March 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 April 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 May 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 June 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 July 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 Sept. 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1970 Dec. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 Jan. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 March 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 March 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 June 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 July 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 July 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 Aug. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 Aug. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 Sept. 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 Sept. 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 October 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 October 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 December 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1971 December 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 January 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 April 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 June 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 July 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 July 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 August 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 August 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 September 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 September 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 November 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1972 December 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 January 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 May 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 July 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 August 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 August 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 August 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 October 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 November 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 December 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1973 December 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1974 January 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1974 February 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1974 March 9 (Box 17-19)
  - Landsteiner, Karl, 1924-1932; 53 items (Box 20)
    Immunogenetics; Poultry genetics
  - Lanier, Raymond R. (Box 20)
  - La Piana, George (Box 20)
  - Laugier, Henri (Box 20)
  - Lazarus, Richard (Box 20)
  - Lebedeff, G.A. (Box 20)
  - Lederberg, J (Box 20)
  - Lehmann, F.E. (Box 20)
  - Lehmann, Hermann (Box 20)
  - Lennard, Reginald (Box 20)
  - Levene, Howard (Box 20)
  - Levi, Giuseppe (Box 20)
  - Levit, G. (Box 20)
  - Levitan, Max (Box 20)
  - Levy, Fritz (Box 20)
  - Lewontin, Richard Charles, 1959-1973; 28 items (Box 20)
    American Naturalist
    Handler, Philip
    National Academy of Sciences
    Sprague, G.F.
    Stevenson, Alan C.
    Columbia University; Mouse genetics; National Academy of Sciences; Political issues; Poultry genetics; Publication
  - Lidicker, William Z., Jr. (Box 20)
  - Lillirn, Cecil (Box 20)
  - Lindegren, Carl C. (Box 20)
  - Lindstrom, E.W. (Box 20)
  - Lippincott, William A., 1921-1927; 71 items (Box 20)
    Bibliographical matters; Genetics -- Nomenclature; Poultry genetics
  - Lisowski, F. Peter (Box 20)
  - Little, C. C. (Clarence Cook), 1928-1941; 30 items (Box 20)
    Mouse genetics; Publication; Research support; Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory
  - Ludmerer, Kenneth M. (Box 21)
  - Lund, Roald (Box 21)
  - Lurie, M.H. (Box 21)
  - Lush, J.L. (Box 21)
  - Lydenberg, Harry Miller, 1938-1941; 25 items (Box 21)
    Brecht, Arnold
    Flexner, Jennie M.
    Kotschnig, W.
    Displaced German scholars; Political issues; Scientific refugees
  - Lynd, Robert (Box 21)
  - Lyon, Mary F. (Box 21)
  - Lysenko Controversy in the US, 1945-1949; 61 items (Box 21)
    Political issues; Publication; Russian politics and science -- Lysenko, Trofim Denisovich; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Lysenko and Voirlov (Publications) (Box 21)
  - McDowell, Carleton (Box 21)
  - MacDowell, E.C. (Box 21)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1931-1969; 92 items (Box 21)
    Renner, Otto
    Sinnott, E.W.
    Business; Editorial matters; Publication -- McGraw-Hill Book Company
  - MacInnes, Duncan (Box 21)
    Dunlap, R.C.
  - McKee, Ralph H. (Box 21)
  - The MacMillan Company (Box 21)
  - Malcovati, Piero (Box 21)
  - Mangelsdorf, Paul C. (Box 21)
  - Mann, A.R. (Box 21)
  - Mann, W.M. (Box 21)
  - Martin, J. Holmes (Box 21)
  - Marvanova, L. (Box 21)
  - Mary Jean, Sister (Box 21)
  - Mather, Kirtley F. (Box 21)
  - Mayr, Ernst (Box 21)
  - Meadowcroft, C.P. (Box 21)
  - Medvedev/Lerner on T-R (Box 21)
  - Mendel Centenary Clippings (Box 22)
  - Mendel material in Martha Washington College (Box 22)
  - Merriam, John C. (Box 22)
  - Mexican Friends of the American People (Box 22)
  - Meyerhoff, Howard A. (Box 22)
  - Michie, Donald, May 1952 (Box 22)
    One letter from L. C. Dunn.
  - Mohr, Jan Gunnar Faye (Box 22)
  - Mohr, Otto Louis, 1929-1967; 76 items (Box 22)
    "Conferring of degree of PhD. on Winston Churchill"
    Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters; History of biology, especially genetics; Political issues; Publication -- Reprints; Recommendations; Russian politics and science; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Mohr, Otto and Tove (Box 22)
  - Montalenti, G. (Box 22)
  - Moody, Julia (Box 22)
  - Morgan, Thomas Hunt, 1918-1945; 21 items (Box 22)
    Kornfeld, A.
    Terzian, A.
    Biographical and personal data -- Mohr, Otto Louis; Biographical and personal data -- Muller, Hermann Joseph; Recommendations -- Belar, Karl; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Morrison, Robert S. (Box 22)
  - Morse, Leighton B. (Box 22)
  - Moscow, England, Denmark, Germany, 1927 (Box 22)
    Genetics
    Hutchinson, C.B.
  - Mossige, Mrs. Jeanne Coyne (Box 22)
  - Mourant, Arthur E. (Box 22)
  - Muller, H. J. (Hermann Joseph), 1928-1967; 61 items (Box 22)
    Cole, L.J.
    Crane, W.M.
    Davies, Mr.
    Genetics Soc. of Amer.
    Gregg, Alan
    Kinsey, A.C.
    Shipley, R.B.
    Weaver, W.
    Drosophila genetics; Human genetics -- Race; Political issues; Publication; Recommendations -- Gershenson, S. M.; Research support; Russian politics and science; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 22)
  - Myerson, Abraham (Box 22)
  - Nachtsheim, Hans (Box 22)
    Cook
    Jervis, George A.
    Winternetz, Milton C.
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1943-1972; 48 items (Box 22)
    Bronk, Detlev
    Cattell, Ware
    Cleland, Ralph
    Edsall, John T.
    Eisner, Thomas
    Gordon, Myron
    Haimson, F.
    Hall, E. Raymond
    Metz, C.W.
    Moulton, F.R.
    Osterhout, W.J.V.
    Owen, Ray
    Seitz, Frederick
    Sinnott, Edmund W.
    Sonnenblick, B.P.
    Sorm, Frantisek
    Woodruff, Lorande Loss
    Wright, Fred
    Biographical and personal data; Congratulations, greetings, thanks; National Academy of Sciences; Political issues; Publication; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - National Research Council - Committee on experimental animals and plants, 1928-1932; 175 items (Box 22)
    Committee activities -- Committee on experimental animals and plants; Genetics; National Research Council; Research support
  - National Science Foundation (Box 23)
    Carlson, Elof Axel
    Shapere, Dudley
  - Naturalists (Box 23)
    Agassiz, Alexander
    Agassiz, Louis J.R.
    American Society of Naturalists
    Norton, Charles Eliot
    White, A.D.
  - Nehama, J. (Box 23)
    Schiby, Alleyra
  - Nevis Newsletter (Box 23)
  - New American Library, 1957-1971; 4 folders
    Business; Publication
    - New American Library [data on publications by LCD] (Box 23)
    - New American Library [revision of Heredity, Race & Society] (Box 23)
  - The New Republic: Malcolm Cowley (Box 23)
  - New York Tribune clipping (Box 23)